http://www.hepafilters.com/privacy-policy/

The Complete Source For All Your Air Filtration & Cleanroom Needs
1-800-523-9852
Home
Air Purifier ProductsAirpura 600 SeriesHM SeriesWhole House ModelsCleanroom ProductsAir ShowersCleaning AgentsCleanroom FurnitureCleanroomsGarmentsHand Sanitation ProductsHEPA VacuumsLaminar Flow BenchesMops & SpongesPAPR (Portable HEPA System)Particle CountersPortable Isolation Room Filtration SysShoe CleanersStainless Steel Pass-ThrusStatic Control (Ionizing Products)Storage ContainersTacky MatsTrash ReceptaclesWipesFilter ProductsAdvanced Air Handling EquipmentCarbonFilter Housing UnitsASHRAE/Prefilter HousingsBag-in/Bag-out HousingsCarbon HousingsHEPA/ULPA HousingsFilter ModulesPrefiltersPrimary HEPA/ULPA FiltersSecondary ASHRAE Filters Latest News
Careers
About
Contact Us
Clickable Cleanroom
HomePrivacy Policy
Search:
Questions or Concerns? Feel free to give us a call about your specific cleanroom needs or to discuss any questions, comments, or concerns that you may have.
Call Us Toll-Free 1.800.523.9852
Shopping Cart
Your shopping cart is empty
Latest News
Product Categories
Air Purifier Products
Cleanroom Products
Filter Products
At Controlled Environment Certification Services (CECS Inc.), a subsidiary of
STERIS Corporation, we may use the information we collect to determine buying
trends and to provide a more personalized experience on the site. Please read on
for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect and how do we use it?
For
promotional features, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so
we can distribute promotional offerings, administer contests, and notify
winners. We monitor Customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop
the design and layout of the site, determine Customer preferences and otherwise
review product offerings and trends. We may also use the information we collect
to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the Web
site, new products or services, and special offers we think you’ll find
valuable.
What about “Cookies”?
“Cookies” are small pieces of
information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our
cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do
enable us to provide features such as personalized shopping and to store items
in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept
cookies.
Will CECS Inc. disclose the information it collects to outside
parties?
CECS Inc. does not currently sell, trade, or rent your
personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future. Also, CECS
Inc. may provide aggregate statistics about our Customers, sales, traffic
patterns, and related site information to third-party vendors, but these
statistics currently include no personally identifying information.
Your consent.
By using our Web site, you consent to the
collection and use of this information by CECS, Inc. If we decide to change our
privacy policy, we will post our revised policy on this page so that you are
always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what
circumstances we disclose it. By using our site, you also agree to our Terms of
Use and Terms of Sale. CECS, Inc. is not liable for any direct, indirect,
special, consequential or other damages that may arise from any violation of
this Policy.
© Copyright 2020 Cleanroom Filters & Supplies. All Rights Reserved. Florida Web Design Privacy Policy
